▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 决赛
菲斯 6-3 1-6 6-0 蒂亚福 · 赛后捧杯致辞
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士们，先生们，
your champion is Sir Arthur Fils.
你们的冠军是——亚瑟·菲斯。
To present Arthur with that Rookwood Cup,
为亚瑟颁发这尊奖杯的，
Mr.
鲍勃
Bob Moran.
·莫兰。
And Arthur, we'd love to hear from you.
亚瑟，我们想听你说几句。
Okay, my turn now.
好，轮到我了。
Hello everyone.
大家好。
I mean, first I have to start with with you,
首先，我想先说说你，
Francis.
弗朗西斯。
I mean, man, it's good to be to be here
说真的，能站在这里
to play a final against you.
跟你打这场决赛，真好。
You know, when I was young,
你知道吗，我小时候，
I was watching you a lot on TV.
经常在电视上看你打球。
You are one of the guy
你是那种
that that make me turn on the TV.
会让我专门打开电视看的人。
So, I'm very very happy to see a lot
所以，能打出这么多
of nice battle.
精彩的对攻，我特别开心。
Of course, congrats to the team as well.
当然，也要恭喜你的团队。
I mean,
真的，
you guys are making unbelievable job.
你们做得太出色了。
So, thank you. Congrats.
谢谢你们，恭喜。
Now I want to to thanks the crowd.
现在我想谢谢现场的观众。
I mean, even if today you were not cheering
就算今天你们没有为我
for me, but that was a hell of a week.
加油，这一周也太精彩了。
Now I want to say thanks to my team.
现在我想谢谢我的团队。
I mean guys, unbelievable.
真的，你们太了不起了。
I have no words I cannot say except thank
我不知道还能说什么，只能说
you.
谢谢。
Thank you very much, guys.
太谢谢你们了。
Thank you, Eva and Lapo, Hank, everyone.
谢谢伊娃、拉波、汉克。
Back in Europe, we made a hell of a job
在欧洲，我们下了很大功夫，
and it's not done yet.
而且还没有结束。
And, you know, I've been traveling
你知道吗，这段时间
with my dad every week.
我一直带着爸爸满世界跑。
He he's not here now.
他现在不在这儿。
I won the trophy, but I would just want
我拿到了奖杯，但我还是想
to say thanks to him as well.
跟他说一声谢谢。
Thanks to all my family.
谢谢我所有的家人。
They are back in Europe.
他们都在欧洲。
Thanks you guys.
谢谢你们。
And of course, just to finish,
最后，
thanks to Cincinnati,
谢谢辛辛那提，
thanks to the tournament.
谢谢这项赛事。
I mean, it's been a hell of a week,
这一周太精彩了，
and I will come back next year.
明年我还会回来。
Arthur, if I can get you to stand right here,
亚瑟，请你站到这儿来，
hold that trophy up high.
把奖杯高高举起。
May I present to you everybody your 2026
有请——2026 年
Cincinnati Open men's singles champion,
辛辛那提公开赛男单冠军，
Arthur Fils.
亚瑟·菲斯。